SUJIT SAH

F-1/b Nawada Housing Complex, Gali no-9 Near dwarka mor new delhi 59
New Delhi, 110059
+919650953245
sujitsah60@gmail.com

Summary

A result oriented professional with 1.5+ years of experience in application development using technologies like SAP ABAP and front end technologies.

Insightful knowledge of applications built using ABAP(back end) and web technologies(javascript, html, bootstrap, node).

Employment History

Accenture Gurugram, Haryana
Associate Software Engineer December 2017 - Present

Working as SAP developer - Building Application in ABAP.

Intern(Javascript developer)

MYCROSIS SOFTWARE SOLUTIONS

Intern

New Delhi, Delhi January 2017 - May 2017

June 2016 - August 2016

Professional Skills

QuickCompany

Javascript	****
C++	****
node.js	****
Abap	****
Data Structures	****
HTML5	****
Bootstrap	****
AngularJS	****
MySQL	****
Git	****

Education

Oxford sr. sec. school

High School Diploma

Class 10 and Class 12

New Delhi, Delhi Graduated March 2013

Previous projects

- Developed Application using AbAP and Javascript .
- Created a Chat app using node.js and socket.io. It's a chatting application where people can have conversation in a group.
- Developed a blog" techsmartsite.wordpress.com" using WordPress.
- Designed a Portfolio and various static webpage using Bootstrap, HTML/CSS, javascript and jquery.
- · Created Bookmarks application in javascript.
- Created a TO DO list in angular.
- Implement Google Sheet API to fetch data from submit form to a google sheet dynamically.

Hobbies & Interests

Technology Enthusiast ,Food lover,Photography and Bike Riding

Useful links

Portfolio: sujitsah.tk

Github: https://github.com/sujitsah

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/sujit-sah-60/